MUSA ÇEKCEN

FULLSTACK
WEB-DEVELOPER

PROFILE DETAILS

Born Date : 14/11/1982

Marital Status : Married

Work Permit:
Permanent Work Permit in EU

PROFILE INFO

"Expressing my aim to pursue to begin my journey at university by specializing in web development. Focusing on the enhancement of design skills and aligning with relevant guidance is crucial to me. Equipped with training in web development and design, I dedicated a year to studying UI design and am currently enrolled in a 1.5-year web development course. Known for being highly motivated, friendly, empathetic, and determined, my passion lies in both design and development. Exploring color and design concepts brings me great pleasure."

CONTACT





0171-283-2772



cekcen14@gmail.com



Alte Poststrasse 39, 79588 Mappach/Efringen-Kirchen

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jun 2021 - Jan 2023

Home Office Berlin Meta Inc., Digital Marketing Expert

- The provision of strategies and advice to Facebook advertisers is dependent on the algorithm and the long-term target is determined by their budget and need.
- Monitor ongoing marketing campaigns and assess the common topics and creative approaches with the target
- It is important to identify any overlap in audiences and to provide guidance on the next steps for their target.

Jan 2016 - Okt 2017

İstanbul/Turkey

Jolly-Tour., Senior Manager

- Recruitment and training of sales personnel
- Responsible as a Sales Manager
- Advice and support for customers
- New customer acquisition
- Organization, planning and execution of long-distance voyages

Okt 2013 - May 2016

Başarı Publications Bookstore., Sales Expert

istanbul/Turkey

- The role involves responsibility for sales
- Suggesting books that are suitable for the user
- After-sales support and problem solving.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- Turkish Native Language
- English C1
- German A2

MY EXPERTISE

AS A DESIGNER

Web Design

Logo Design

Graphic Design

Adobe XD

Illustrator

Photoshop

AS A DEVELOPER

Javascript	••••
HTML 5	••••
CSS	••••
SCSS	••••
React	••••
Node.js	••••
MongoDB	••••

Nov 2011 - April 2013

istanbul/Turkey

Grimor., Junior Web-Dev

- Website design
- Logo Design

Oct 2009 - May 2011

İstanbul/Turkey

Linna Agency., Graphic Designer-Internship

- Website interface designs
- Logo designs and updates

Jan 2007 - Oct 2007

İstanbul/Turkey

Başarı Computer Ltd.,

Software Engineer - Internship

- ERP program installation and postinstallation technical support
- Helping companies grow and become a more corporate company
- Developing program software

EDUCATION HISTORY

February 2004 - May 2005

New Port International Uni.

Computer Engineer

• Academic Preparatory Class

Website and Mobile App developmentFront-End and Back-End education

February 2005 - May 2009

New Port International Uni.

Computer Engineer

• Bachelor of Engineering

COURSE & CERTIFICATES

August 2023 - Continue

DCI - Digital Career Institute

September 2020 -January 2021

Carrier Foundry Online UI Course

2020 - UI Designer

• Web and App UI Design

January 2013 - July 2014

Bilge Adam Graphic & Design Course

Designer

Logo DesignWeb Design

Web-Developer

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Book Shop:

Developed by React, CSS

Link: https://todo-list-njrx.onrender.com

Jewellaru Website:

Project (HTML-CSS)

Link: https://ilkckn.github.io/Jewellery-ECommerce

Watch E-commerce:

Website Project (React)

Link: https://watche-commerce.onrender.com

And more